var questions = [
  {
    question: "Are you happy?",
    choices: ["Eh", "Why not"],
    answer: ["Eh", "Why not"]
  },
  {
    question: "How are you enjoying class?",
    choices: ["I love it", "Please end me"],
    answer: ["I love it", "Please end me"]
  },
  {
    question: "JavaScript's creator's muse was cocaine.",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "What have you given up to be here?",
    choices: ["Just Money", "My soul"],
    answer: ["Just Money", "My soul"]
  },
  {
    question: "How awesome is Alex?",
    choices: ["Only by a lot!", "That'll do pig"],
    answer: ["Only by a lot!", "That'll do pig"]
  },
  {
    question: "Is true true?",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "Is false true?",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    question: "Will we have robot overlords?",
    choices: ["Yes, I'm ready to be a sub", "No, never"],
    answer: "Yes, I'm ready to be a sub"
  },
  {
    question: "Is resistance futile?",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "Do you want a high-paying job or plenty of free time?",
    choices: ["Yes"],
    answer: "Yes"
  },
  {
    question: "Is the word moist unnerving?",
    choices: ["Yes *shudders*", "It excites me"],
    answer: ["Yes *shudders*", "It excites me"]
  },
  {
    question: "Is this class worth it?",
    choices: ["Every penny", "Too late now"],
    answer: "Too late now"
  },
  {
    question: "Will you review over break?",
    choices: ["No, I understand everything perfectly", "Does a cow moo??"],
    answer: "Does a cow moo??"
  },
  {
    question: "If a tree falls and no one is there to hear it, does it make a sound?",
    choices: ["Yes", "No"],
    answer: "Yes"
  },
  {
    question: "You need a coding background to be successful in this class.",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    question: "Does absolute power corrupt absolutely?",
    choices: ["Yes, always", "No"],
    answer: "No"
  },
  {
    question: "Technological progress is inevitable.",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "Life requires a purpose.",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    question: "Pseudocoding is your friend.",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "One more time, is false false?",
    choices: ["True", "Stahp"],
    answer: ["True", "Stahp"]
  }

];